Finding Aid for the Bound Manuscripts Collection LSC.0170
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Bound Manuscripts
  - Bushell, William Done (1838-1917). A Silver Wedding: W.D.B. & M.B. December 20, 1891. (Cambridge: Privately Printed, ). Bound with various works of the author, e.g. Egypt and Elsewhere, and manuscript., 170/110; 18pp.
  - Planché, James Robinson (1796-1880). Legends of the Rhine from Mainz to Köln **Possibly published as Lays and Legends of the Rhine., ca. 1830 1832; 170/111; Manuscript, 62pp., 13 illustrations.
  - Smith, Logan Pearsall (1865-1946). Milton & his Modern Critics. **Rough notes for his Milton and his Modern Critics., ca. 1940 1940; 170/112; Manuscript, 43 leaves.
  - Anacreon. Odaria, ad textus Barnesiani fidem emendata. Accedunt variae lectiones cura Eduardi Forster. (London, ). **Double fore-edge painting: (a) View of Cambridge, including King's College Chapel; (b) view of Oxford, including the Radcliffe Camera., 1802; 170/113
  - Nares, Robert (1753-1829). A Glossary; or, Collection of Words, Phrases, Names, and Allusions to Customs... which have been thought to require Illustration, in the Works of English Authors, particularly Shakespeare, and his Contemporaries (London )., 1822; *170/114; **Author's copy, with copious manuscript notes.
  - Nitze, William Albert (1876-1957). The Old French Grail romance Perlesvaus: a Study of its Principal Sources (Baltimore )., 1902; 170/115; **Author's interleaved copy, with manuscript notes, and letters to Nitze.
  - Sloan, John (b. 1871). The Gist of Art: Principles and Practice expounded in the Classroom and Studio (New York ). **Tipped in are letters from Sloan about an exhibition of the artist's paintings., 1939; 170/116
  - Ireland, William Henry (1777-1835). The Confessions of William Henry Ireland. Containing the Particulars of his Fabrication of the Shakespeare Manuscripts (London, ). **A defective copy, but extra-illustrated throughout (ca. 1828)., 1805; 170/117
  - S., M.D. compiler. Recueil de pieces de vers de differents auteurs (Paris, ). Commonplace Book., 1728; 170/118; Manuscript.
  - Worrell, Edward (d. 1877). A Journal of a Campaign through the South Western and Western Prairies in the Months of May and June 1833. **An account of the campaign against the Pawnees by an Assistant Surgeon in the U.S. Army., 170/119; Manuscript, 130pp.
  - Milton, John (1608-1674). The Poetical Works of John Milton... (London, ). **Fore-Edge Painting with fox-hunting scene., 1859; 170/120
  - Palgrave, Francis Turner (1824-1897), compiler. The Golden Treasury of the Best Songs and Lyrical Poems in the English Language (London )., 1896; 170/121; **Bound in red morocco inlaid with tan and green morocco and covers tooled in gilt, by Ramage (London).
  - Lord Durham and the Mission to Canada ()., 1838; *170/122; Manuscript, 97 leaves.
  - Ince, Thomas Harper (1880-1924). Synopses of Productions made by Thomas H. Ince during the period April 1912 to August 1915 (Inceville Studios). Including alphabetical and numerical indexes to scenarios., *170/123; Typescript, carbon. 486pp.
  - Harlow, Neal (b. 1908). Reference Manual for the Classification, Cataloging and Care of the Map Collection (Sacramento?: California State Library, )., 1950; *170/124; 2 vol. Typescript.
  - Villa, José Garcia. Have Come, Am Here. Poems (New York, 1942). **Annotated by Edith Sitwell for a projected edition, apparently never published, of Villa's poems., 170/125
  - Nathan, Robert (b. 1894). Portrait of Jennie. **First published by Knopf in 1940., *170/126; Manuscript/Typescript. Three versions, two folders.
  - Munro, William Bennett (1875-1957). The Seigneurial System and the Colony (Toronto 1914-1917). **From Canada and its Provinces ed. A. Shortt/A.G. Doughty (Glasgow )., 1914/17; 170/127; Page proofs with copious holograph corrections, pp.531-593, and vol.2.
  - Cronyn, George William (b. 1888). The Fool of Venus [the Story of Peire Vidal] (New York )., 1934; 170/128; **Galley proofs, 391pp.
  - Stebbins, Oliver B. A Famous Boston Amateur Dramatic Club. **A published article, source unknown, mounted on a specially bound book, with original photographs, prints, playbills etc. On backstrip: The Aurora Club., ca. 1893; 170/170/129; 46pp.
  - Egbert, Eliza Ann (McAuley) (b. 1835). Diary. **Diary of a journey by wagon from Iowa to Sacramento. Copy made by the author's son in, April 7-September 19, 1852 January 1935.; *170/130; Typescript copy.
  - Carr, William Jarvis (1879-1959). Journals (1903-1905). **Record of Carr's activities as member of the Office of the Prosecuting Attorney, Manila, and the law firm of Gale & Gibbs in Manila, The Philippines., 170/131: 1-3; 3 vol. Manuscript.
  - U.S. Post Office, Duarte, California. Record and Postal Account Book, Class 4. **Entries by A.W. Holdzkom and James Fowler, Postmasters at Duarte., April 1892-December 31, 1894; *170/132; 26pp. printed form.
  - Van Rensselear, C. Account Book, Jefferson Barracks, Mo. **Account book of 1st Lieutenant Van Rensselear, Adjutant of 13th Infantry, Jefferson Barracks, as Recruiting Officer for the General Recruiting Depot., September 21, 1861-October 17, 1862; 170/133; 1 vol.
  - Pierce, Charles C. Accounts. **Journals and ledgers of the Los Angeles photographer., 1909-1921; *170/134:1-8; 8 vol.
  - Holt, Frances (Long). Journal. **Journal of trip from Knutsford, Cheshire, England, to America, via St. Thomas, V.I., Havana, and return from Canada. There are descriptions of New Orleans, St Louis, Kansas City, Denver, San Francisco, the Geysers near Geyserville, California, Merced, the Yosesmite Valley, Salt Lake City, Chicago, Niagara Falls, New York, Boston, Kingston, Montreal, Quebec, and other places along the route between these cities. The author was the second wife of Alfred Holt of Alfred Holt & Company, Liverpool, a pioneer steamship line to the Far East., April 1-July 29, 1872; Manuscript, 151pp.
  - Index to the California Land Claims., vol.1-24 (and miscellaneous vols.). Typescript, 28 leaves.
  - Souvenirs de la Commune 23 Mai 1871. Fragments de papiers brules provenant du ministere des finances et projetes jusque dans la cour de ma maison rue Niccolo 10 ou ils ont été ramasses (Paris )., ca. 1860/1871; *170/137; **14 fragments mounted on five leaves.
  - Morrison, Arthur (1863-1945). Letter, signed, to James William Thomas Ley, Loughton, Sussex. **With clippings about Morrison., August 21, 1908; 170/138
  - Campbell, Roy (1901-1957). Adamastor, Poems. **This is the only complete manuscript of my book 'Adamastor'--Roy Campbell. First published, London, 1930.; *170/139; Manuscript, 57 leaves.
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931). Polite Farces for the Drawing-Room (London, ). **Annotated throughout with stage directions by Stanley Hazell; Autograph letter signed from Bennett to Mr. and Mrs. Hazell, 1900 September 19, 1899.; 170/140
  - Lancey, Thomas Crosby (1824-1885). The Cruise of the Dale, ed. John Haskell Kemble (Pomona )., ca. 1946; *170/141; Typescript. xi, 265, [53] leaves, extensively corrected.
  - Haupt, Paul (1858-1926). Prof. Delitzsch. Hebraeische Grammatik im Anschluss an Gesenius-Rödiger. Sommer-Semester 1876 (Leipzig )., 170/142; 166 leaves.
  - Russell, Thomas. Thomas Russell, his Manuscript of Navigation. Royal Academy, 1746., *170/143; Manuscript, 194pp., illustrations.
  - Caldwell, Edmund G. (b. 1852). [Illustrations for] A Gaping Wide-Mouth Waddling Frog., 170/144; Original water-colour paintings. 11 items.
  - Cornish, Mrs Beatrice (Quijada) (b. 1878). Francisco Navarro Villoslada, su vida y su obra (Berkeley ). **First published in 1918., ca. 1918; *170/145; Typescript, 296 leaves, illustrations.
  - Sutton, Ernest Venable (b. 1862). A Life Worth Living: Pioneering in Ohio, Minnesota, Dakota and California (South Pasadena ). **First published Pasadena 1948., 1947; *170/146; Typescript, 387 leaves.
  - Ryan, Don. Angel's Flight. **A collection of short pieces, mostly having Los Angeles as their locale. First published, New York, 1927.; *170/147; Typescript carbon, 297 leaves.
  - Harlow, Neal (b. 1908). History of Costume (Los Angeles s.a.). **Paper prepared for Mrs Sooy's Art 103, UCLA., *170/148
  - Beck, Frederick K./Barnes, O.K. 73 Years in a Sand Trap. **First published, New York, 1949.; *170/149; Typescript, 108 leaves.
  - Griffith, Beatrice Winston. American Me. **First published, Boston, 1948.; *170/150; Typescript, 446+ leaves. Printer's copy.
  - Howard, Sidney Coe (1891-1939)/De Kruif, Paul. Yellow Jack, a History. **First published, New York 1934. Accompanied by original sketches for the stage production by Jo Mielziner., *170/151; Typescript carbon, 147 leaves.
  - O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone (1888-1953). Strange Interlude: a Play in Nine Acts. **Presentation copy from Jo Mielziner. First published, New York 1928., ca. 1927; *170/152; Typescript carbon, 438 leaves.
  - O'Neill, Eugene Gladstone (1888-1953). Note, unsigned, to Robert Sisk. **Concerns O'Neill's plans for future plays., February 24, 1932; *170/153; Manuscript.
  - Viertel, Peter (b. 1920). The Canyon. **First published, New York 1940., ca. 1939; *170/154; Typescript.
  - Hancock, Ralph (b. 1903). Fabulous Boulevard (Los Angeles, ). **Printer's copy. First published, New York 1949. Accompanied by Publisher's Dummy (170/155: 2)., ca. 1949; *170/155: 1; Typescript, 347pp.
  - Foley, James William (b. 1874). The Will of Manitou: an Allegory in Four Scenes (Pasadena )., 1920; 170/156; Typescript, 37 leaves.
  - New Orleans. North, Central and South American Exposition (1885-1886). Board of State and Territorial Commisioners. Minutes, New Orleans. **The minutes are in the handwriting of Charles B. Turrill, Secretary of the Board and Commissioner for California., November 7, 1885-March 31, 1886; 2 vol. manuscript.
  - Southern California Abstract Company, Los Angeles and the Los Angeles Abstract Company Continuation of abstract of title as to 74 acres of land within the limits of the Guirado tract of the Rancho Paso de Bartolo Viejo, County of Los Angeles, California., March 13, 1888-May 13, 1889; *170/158; Manuscript and printed forms, 45 leaves.
  - Great Britain. Colonial Office. Reports and papers respecting Lower Canada and New Foundland (1790-1792). Lower Canada., *170/159; vol.62 A, Part 1. Photostats. 101 leaves.
  - Stamps, Pearl Pauline. Abel Stearns: California Pioneer, 1798-1871 (Berkeley ). **Thesis, University of California, Berkeley., 1925; Typescript carbon. viii, 474 leaves.
  - Busch, Niven (b. 1903). Duel in the Sun. **A novel first published, New York, 1944.; *170/161; Typescript, 413 leaves.
  - Childs, Emeline. Ledger of Accounts for Estate of Orzo W. Childs, Los Angeles., 1890-1891; *170/162; Manuscript, 401 leaves.
  - Blair, William (1766-1822). Letters and clippings. **These materials concern Joseph Powell, an astrologer, who was convicted in London on October 30, 1807 for vagrancy and extracting money under false pretences from Thomas Barnes, a footman in the employ of William Blair, a surgeon in Gt Russell Street, Bloomsbury., 1807-1808; *170/163; Manuscripts and clippings (mounted), 37pp.
  - Union of Democratic Control. London Branch. Minutes. **Minutes of the Association for the Right Understanding of International Interests and the Civil Union, predecessors of the London Branch of the Union of Democratic Control., January 23, 1913-February 11, 1917; 170/164; Manuscript, 161pp.
  - Carrington's Planatations, Barbados, W.I. Accounts (1810-1855). **Includes journal entries for the four Carrington sugar planatations of David Parris and his heirs, Anna Maria Carrington, wife of George Carrington, and Paul Carrington Parris., *170/165: 1-3; Manuscript. 3 vol.
  - North, George (1710-1772). Letters to Andrew C. Ducarel, Codicote, Hertfordshire. Letters concerning North's antiquarian studies on early Saxon coins and English churches. **Some of these letters are published in John Nichols, Literary Anecdotes of the 18th Century 5, London 1812, pp.427 sqq. Phillipps manuscript 9447., March 21,1743-December 21, 1754; **170/166; Manuscript, 12 letters.
  - My Uncle's Will: an Interlude in 2 Acts. **This play is different from that of the same title by Spenser Theyre Smith., ca. 1833; 170/167; Manuscript, 51 leaves.
  - Colton, Ray Charles (b. 1907). The Civil War in the Western Territories: Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico and Utah (Los Angeles, ). **Published by the University of Oklahoma Press, 1959., August 1959; *170/168; Typescript. Printer's copy.
  - Sahagun, Bernardino (d. 1590). General History of Things in New Spain, vol.1. Translated from the Spanish...by Gabriel S. Yorke (Los Angeles, ). **Not completed., 1945; *170/169; Typescript, 330 leaves.
  - Lowell, Amy (1874-1925). The Bronze Horse, from Can Grande's Castle (Brookline, Massachusetts ). **First published, New York 1918., ca. 1918; *170/170; Typescript, 5 leaves.
  - Lowell, Amy (1874-1925). Six French Poets: Studies in Contemporary Literature (New York )., 1915; *170/171; Corrected Proof sheets. 239 sheets.
  - Moore, George (1852-1933). Confessions of a Young Man (London, )., 1888; 170/172; Corrected Proof Sheets for pp.243-387.
  - Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbiter-Partei. Documents from the Nazi Party Archive., 1920-1927; *170/173; Photostats. 3 items.
  - Ajaccio. Manifesto della municipalita della citta d'Ajaccio: Dipartimento di Corsica (Ajaccio, ). **Concerns the battalions of the National Guard of the districts of Ajaccio and Tallano during the French Revolution., April 8, 1792; *170/174; Manuscript, 19pp.
  - Ainsworth, William Harrison (1805-1882). The Flitch of Bacon. Part the Sixth (Monksbury Place, ). **Early drafts of Part the Fourth (sic) of a novel, first published, London 1854., ca. 1854; 170/175; Manuscript, 88 leaves.
  - Browne, Charles Farrar (1834-1867). Artemus Ward's Lecture as delivered at the Egyptian Hall, London [November 13, 1866 (London, 1866-1868). **First published, London, 1869., *170/176; Manuscript with associated drawings and letters.
  - Allen, William. Geographical, Historical and Political Observations upon the Several Kingdomes and States of Europe for the Use of Madam Jane Tynte, Goathurst, Somerset, Gt Brit. **Said to be from the Library of Lord Wharton., 1721-1722; 170/177; Manuscript, 4 vol.
  - Forrester, Alfred Henry (1804-1872). Notebooks (London ). **Commonplace book containing copies of poems by Forrester and others, notably Letitia Elizabeth Landon., ca. 1850; 170/178; Manuscript, 2 vol.
  - Partington, Wilfred George (b. 1888). Forging Ahead: the True Story of the Upward Progress of Thomas James Wise, Prince of Book Collectors, Bibliographer Extraordinary and otherwise (New York )., 1939; 170/179; **Author's copy, annotated for the second edition of the book.
  - Great Britain. Privy Council. Committee on Education. Draft: Plan of Education by the Rt Hon. the Secretary of State [addressed to John Fane, 10th Earl of Westmoreland] (London ). **Reports on the various kinds of schools in England with observations on them, and a plan for education by which existing abuses would be corrected., ca. 1790; *170/180; Manuscript, 204pp.
  - Plato. Hippias Maior (s.l. s.a.). (Harrow )., 1833; 170/181; pp.121-183, interleaved. **Anthony Trollope's copy, heavily annotated.
  - Harvard University. Body of Laws for Harvard College ... made ... 1734 (Cambridge, Massachusetts ). **Edward A. Holyoke's copy., September 15, 1742; 170/182
  - Weston, William (1752-1833). Account Book (Gainsborough, Lincolnshire, Gt Brit. **Household accounts for the period after Weston's return to England from the U.S.A., 170/183; Manuscript, 158pp. & 9 pieces in pocket.
  - Newspapers. Index to the Washington Daily National Intelligencer., September/December 1852; 170/184; Manuscript.
  - Beauregard, Pierre Gustave Toutant (1818-1893). Commonplace Book (New Orleans, ). **Presented to General Beauregard by Les dames de la Nouvelle Orléans, and containing a five page letter of presentation and dedication. The book was never used., March 12, 1864; 170/185; Manuscript, 5pp.
  - Brougham Hall, Westmoreland, Gt Brit. Record of Work done at Brougham Hall. **A detailed record of the restoration of Brougham Hall by Lord Henry Peter Brougham, 1st Baron Brougham and Vaux., October 28, 1843-March 31, 1849; 170/186; Manuscript, 130pp.
  - Martel, James Louis, comp. U.S. Sloop Dale... Collection of Songs. **Lyrics, including a song about the engagement at Mulyé, Mexico., ca. 1848-1849; 170/187; Manuscript, 52pp.
  - Wimmer, Ludvig Frands Adalbert (1839-1920). De norske Sprogs Historie., 170/188; Manuscript, 420pp.
  - Peretti, J., Abbé. 'Christoph Colomb, Français, Corse & Calvais. Etude historique sur la patrie du grand admiral de l'océan': a Condensation and Full Synopsis...by Ervine Dennison York (Washington )., 1891; 170/189; Typescript, 186 leaves.
    Another copy is in the Library of Congress.
  - Cookery Books. A Cooking Book, with D. Knothesford's Additions (Bristol ). **The last 26 leaves contain medicinal recipes and cures for various illnesses., 1766; 170/190; Manuscript, 92 leaves.
  - La Mure, Pierre. Moulin Rouge. **Novel based on the life of Henri Toulouse-Lautrec. Published, 1950., ca. 1950; *170/191; Typescript, 632 leaves.
  - Denovan, Robert. A Treatise of the Elements of the Algebraical Art. **With an introductory poem, The Tipling Philosophers., 1731; 170/192; Manuscript, 185 leaves.
  - Arithmetic Book. (English )., 1721; 170/193; Manuscript, 48pp.
  - Burnet, John (1784/1868). Practical Hints on Light and Shade in Painting, illustrated by Examples from Italian, Flemish and Dutch Schools. **First published, 1826. Seventeen original illustrations at end., ca. 1826; 170/194; Manuscript, 67pp.
  - Perizonius, Jacobus (1651-1715). Dictata ... in Cajum Suetonium Tranquillum., ca. 1700; 170/195; Manuscript, 335pp.
  - Renison, Thomas (1751/1817). Commonplace-Book (London). **Verse and prose; the final four pages are devoted to genealogical notes on the Renison family., 1775; 170/196; Manuscript, 33pp.
  - Maberly, Joseph J. Silver Coinage of England: from the conquest to the Reign of James II. **Illustrated throughout with original watercolours of coins., 1838; 170/197; Manuscript, 44 leaves.
  - Morgan, Sydney (Owenson), Lady (1783?-1859). Commonplace Books, containing Poems and Prose by Various Authors. **Both in English and French., 1800-1810; Manuscript, 3 vol.
  - Jacobus de Voragine. Legenda Aurea (Northern France, s. XV med.). **Probably written at the Celestin monastery of Ste-Croix-sous Offémont (Ile de France). Cf. Ferrari 55-58., 170/199; Manuscript, 268 leaves.
  - Foster, Robert A. (b. 1877). Mexico: an Economic Study., *170/200; Typescript, 756 leaves. **Includes 25 tables and seven maps.
  - Crane, Walter (1845-1915). Lionel's Latitudes (Rome ). **A book of original watercolour and pen-and-ink drawings. The hero is the author's son., 1882; 170/201; Manuscript, 53 leaves.
    See also: no.170/315: Lionel's Travels.
  - Dakin, Susanna (Bryant) (b. 1905). A Scotch Paisano (San Marino s.a.). Published, Berkeley, 1939.; Typescript, 335 leaves.
  - Macpherson, James (1736-1796), translator. The Poems of Ossian (London, ). **Fore-edge painting of Horace Walpole's home, Strawberry Hill., 1819; 170/203
  - Besant, Sir Walter (1836-1901). A Note on the Young Girl. **Perhaps unpublished., 170/204; Manuscript, 7 leaves.
  - [Marcet, Mrs Jane (Haldimand] (1769-1858).] Conversations on Astronomy in which the Elements of that Science are familiarly explained and illustrated by plates. Designed for the use of Schools and Academies (s.l. s.a.). **Apparently unpublished., 170/205; Manuscript, 240 leaves.
  - [Millias, F.] Les figures de la danse allemande. **Twelve water-colour illustrations., ca. 1780; 170/206; Manuscript, 12 leaves.
  - [Bowles, Carington (1724-1793).] The Artist's Assistant in Drawing, Perspective, Etching, Engraving, Mezzotinto-Scraping, Painting on Glass, in Crayons, and in Water-Colours (London ). Second edition., ca. 1780; 170/207; **Interleaved with 18pp. of notes and 24 water-colour paintings, mostly views of Gibraltar.
  - Surin, Jean Joseph (1600-1665). Lettres (French ?). **Perhaps a copy of his Lettres spirituelles (Paris, 1704)., ca. 1775; 170/208; Manuscript, 2 vol.
  - [Beerbohm, Max.] The Anglo-Saxon Review: a Quarterly Miscellany, edited by Lady Randolph Spencer Churchill. vol.10. **Ex libris: Max Beerbohm, who has altered the plates opposite pages 63 and 66. Lacking pp.205-214., September 1901; *170/209
  - Smith, Albert Richard (1816-1860). A Little Talk about Bartholomew Fair--Past and Present. **First published, Bentley's Miscellany 12, 1842, p.390., 170/210; Manuscript, 8 leaves.
  - [Ruffini, Giovanni Domenico (1807-1881).] The Paragreens on a Visit to the Paris Universal Exhibition. **First published, London 1856., ca. 1856; 170/211; Manuscript, 77 leaves.
  - Troubetskoy, Amélie (Rives) Chanler (1863-1945). A Winter-Walk (unpublished Poem) and [12] Letters of Amélie Rives...written to me [Edward Heron-Allen] in New York in the Year 1888 (Castle Hill, Cobham, Virginia, February 22, 1888-January 28, 1889)., 170/212; Manuscript, 95pp.
  - Saddharmapundarika. Lotus sutra, section 11. (Japanese 1668). **Frontispiece of cut gold leaf: the Sakyamuni Buddha preaching the Lotus sutra; title is woven in with gold and crest of the Tokugawa family., *170/213; A scroll, 24 feet long by 12 wide.
  - Scott-Moncrieff, Charles Kenneth (1889-1930). Collection of ten early literary manuscripts, prize poems clipped from the newspapers in which they appeared, and four letters to Christopher Sclater Millard. **Previously owned by Millard and Vyvyan Holland., ca. 1905/1916; 170/214
  - Greenaway, Kate (1846-1901). Drawing in Sepia Ink. Original Drawing of a boy and girl at play, initialed by artist., 170/215
  - Wogan, William (1678-1758). The Gospel doctrine of the Divinity, Nature, & Offices of our ever blessed Lord & Saviour Jesus Christ, as taught & asserted by the Four Evangelists (1728-1730). **Apparently unpublished., 170/216; Manuscript, 2 vol.
  - Butterworth, Edward. Diary (November 12,1848-July 4, 1849). **Diary of voyage from Boston to San Francisco via Cape Horn on board the Bark Euphrasia, and including an account of his activities in San Francisco from Also includes 20 loose pages containing poetry, recipes and a photograph., May 26 till July 4, 1849.; Manuscript, 97pp.
  - Warren, Samuel (1807-1877). Letter to Mr. Osbaldiston (s.l. s.a.). **Includes three portraits of Warren and a 2pp. printed biographical note., 170/218; Manuscript, 1p.
  - Codrington, Sir Edward (1770-1851). Letter (memo) signed, to Captain Michell, Britannia (Portsmouth Harbour ). **With portraits of C. and Lady Georgiana Codrington., May 1, 1840; 170/219; Manuscript, 1p.
  - Stokes, George Gabriel (1819-1903). Letters, signed, to Jabez Hogg (London, and Cambridge ). **Accompanied by two documents, signed by Stokes, adddressed to Hogg, and a portrait of Stokes., 1877 1882; 170/220; Manuscripts, 2 items.
  - Spencer, George John Spencer, 2nd Earl (1758-1834). Letter, signed, to David Scott. **Accompanied by seven portraits of, and relating to, George and John Charles Spencer., April 6, 1797; 170/221; Manuscript, 1p.
  - Bickersteth, Edward, Dean (1814-1892). Letters, signed, to various persons (1879-1884). Manuscript, 4 items. **Two letters to Jabez Hogg (), J.R. Keble (1884). Accompanied by five portraits and an obituary notice., 1883; 1884; 170/222
  - Leicester, Thomas William Coke, Earl of (1752-1842). Letters, signed (Holkham, ). **Accompanied by three portraits of Coke and press cuttings., March 16, 1798; 170/223; Manuscript, 1p.
  - Shee, Sir Martin Archer (1769-1850). Letters, signed, to various persons (London,; s.a.). **Two letters to Alfred Turner () and letter to unknown man. Accompanied by two portraits of Shee., March 4, 1831 1831; 170/224; Manuscript, 3 items.